I am studying in English medium I am sleeping without
medicines and there is
increase in foreign trade and responsibilities Ritesh
Lootere is an
Indian name he is doing well he is
Bharti there bread he is of Indian stock
markets [Music] we say
[Music]
quantity voice changer ho par aate shanti
le par aabo bhi shanti
and Sanjay Bhai aim education si vad ko hai he is
recommended without any dependant he is good kind
of brother he is Bharat ki Jai Ho he is
some Punjabi some change amazing me
Jhadpiya is decorated with an arrow till then we are Roy
[Music]
Kiran Shakti Kutark Amazon it was a
misconception hey Meghwar he is Indian people etc etc
and based
ARU
[Music]